There is a small canal, it is a remnant of
小さな管があります。これは
this hyaloid vessel
硝子体動脈の痕跡です。
and a fine canal currently remains in the eye
そして現在も目の中に細い管が残っています。
which leads us directly to a primary axis
それは私たちを直接、最初の重要な
important
軸へと導きます。
which is called Cloquet's canal.
それはクロケ管と呼ばれています。
And you see it here, you see, it's a remnant in this
ここに見えますね。これはこの
humor
体液の中の痕跡です。
you have different humors
様々な体液があります。
this is the humor
これは
aqueous and then the vitreous humor
房水と硝子体液です。
and the vitreous humor
そして硝子体液は、
you really have to imagine
本当に想像してみてください。
that it's like a balloon
それはゼラチン状の水の
of gelatinous water
ボールのようなもので、
that is in the eye
目の中にあり、
that floats
浮いています。
of water
水が
with at its center
その中心に
a fine canal
細い管があり、
which comes directly onto the lens here
それが直接、ここにある水晶体につながっています。
You see, here, which is a direct axis with the
ここに見えますね。これは視神経、または硝子体管と直接つながる軸です。
optic nerve, or the hyaloid canal.
視神経、または硝子体管と直接つながる軸です。
So the lens, it comes from your skin, surface ectoderm.
したがって、水晶体はあなたの皮膚、表面外胚葉から来ています。
Invagination, fifth week, lens vesicle is surrounded by vascularized mesenchyme.
陥入、第5週、水晶体小胞は血管新生した間葉に囲まれています。
Then, I have this connection.
次に、この接続があります。
Juxtacrine, the placode
傍分泌、プラコードが
invaginates and will become
陥入し、
the lens. It's the same movement
水晶体になります。これは神経管と同じ動きです。プフ、トゥク！
as a neural tube. Poof, touc!
神経管と同じ動きです。プフ、トゥク！
Inside, there remains a space,
内部には、
which we call the crystalline lens.
水晶体と呼ばれる空間が残っています。
There is a whole evolution of this crystalline lens
この水晶体には、
which will form
原始的な線などを
primitive lines, etc.
形成する進化の過程があります。
I will skip this part.
それは省略します。
It's important to understand how it forms
それがどのようにして神経管のように形成され、
like a neural tube, and it becomes
そしてここで、それ自体で
here, on its own.
形成されるのかをよく理解することが重要です。
It is truly the lens
それは本当にレンズです。
of the eye.
行為の。
You see here the colobomic fissure; there is a line here
ここにコロムビアの裂け目が見えます。ここに線があります。
below, you see, and that's what will later form, with the arteries, the canal of
その下には、ほら、それが動脈と一緒にクロケ管になるんです。
Cloquet.
クロケ。
It will close with the hyaloid artery and vein, which is central; this
それは中央にある動脈とヒエリオイド静脈で閉じられます。この
important artery, this is a colobomic fissure in the eye
重要な動脈、これは目の中のコロムビアの裂け目です。
that is not closed.
閉じられていない。
What is this?
これは何ですか？
It is the primary lens vesicle
これは一次水晶体小胞です。
which becomes a secondary lens vesicle
それが二次水晶体小胞になります。
with the lens placode; this is the crystalline lens,
プラコードと一緒に、これは水晶体です。
juxtacrine, integration, you see.
傍分泌、統合、ほら。
With the layer.
層と一緒に。
Here, which will form what we call, externally,
ここでは、外側に、いわゆるものを形成します。
it is the sclera, the first coat.
それは強膜、最初の靴下です。
The second coat is here, all
2番目の靴下はここです。これらすべては、実際には脈絡膜です。
of this, in fact, is the choroid
これらすべては、実際には脈絡膜です。
which will form the attachment with the crystalline lens.
水晶体との結合を形成します。
Anterior chamber, posterior chamber in the part.
前房、後房は部分的に。
anterior. So I can divide the eye into parts.
前方。したがって、目を部分的に分割できます。
forward and backward, and in the anterior part, I divide it
前方と後方に、そして前方部分では、それを分割します。
into anterior chambers and posterior chambers. Then, we have
前房と後房に。次に、
what is called the
いわゆる
conjunctiva, the cornea,
結膜、角膜、
which is in continuity, conjunctiva,
連続している、結膜、
cornea, and the cornea is in continuity.
角膜、そして角膜は連続しています。
Continuity with the sclera.
強膜との連続性。
And what do we call the part here,
そして、ここの部分を何と呼びますか？
the second, we called it the choroid.
2番目は脈絡膜と呼びました。
We call it the uvea.
それをブドウ膜と呼びます。
And the uvea, it comes from the Latin uva, which means grape.
そしてブドウ膜は、ラテン語のuva（ブドウを意味する）に由来します。
This small membrane, like this, is a membrane very rich in vessels.
この小さな皮膚は、血管が非常に豊富な皮膚です。
It divides into three.
それは3つに分かれています。
parts, or into two or three major parts, which we call the choroid
部分、または2つか3つの大きな部分で、脈絡膜と呼ばれます。
here, and anteriorly
ここ、そして前方には
the cornea, and the cornea is transparent.
角膜があり、角膜は透明です。
But here posteriorly, there will be the iris, which
しかし、ここ後方には虹彩があり、それは
is a continuity of the choroid, and
脈絡膜の連続性であり、そして
we will have here connections, a ligament.
ここには結合、靭帯があります。
which we call the suspensory ligament of the iris,
虹彩懸靭帯と呼ばれるもの、
which maintains the iris,
虹彩を保持している、
with small muscles called the ciliary muscles,
毛様体筋と呼ばれる小さな筋肉で、
which will...
それが…
We will see that in a bit more detail later.
それは後で詳しく見ていきます。
So the retina, in fact,
網膜は、実際には、
is the innermost layer of the eye.
眼の最も内側の層です。
Do you remember this first vesicle,
この最初の小胞を覚えていますか？
this small sphere that emerges,
この小さな球が飛び出してくる、
which we call the primary optic vesicle.
これを一次視神経胞と呼びます。
which will make a movement like this, you see, like a
それはこのように動きます、わかりますか、まるで
calyx, a vessel.
杯、花瓶のように。
It is made of two layers, an inner layer and an outer layer.
それはこのように2つの層でできています、わかりますか、内側の層と外側の層です。
And this is where one understands what is called a retinal detachment.
そして、ここで網膜剥離と呼ばれるものが理解できます。